에바였어요.
That was Eva.
에바와 세바스찬이 이틀 전 전소된 차에서 흔적을 발견했어요.
Eva and Sebastian found a wreck from two days ago of a burned up car.
그리고?
And?
앤-마리라고 확신하고 있어요.
She's sure it's Anne-Marie's.
Arabela! Arabela...
내 상관이었는데. 날 공격했어.
It was my boss. He attacked me.
- 그사람을 도와주고 있었어.
- 제노비즈가 도망쳤어요.
- He helped him.
- Genovese Escaped.
빠리로 돌아갈거야.
I'm going back to Paris.
- 뭐라고?
- 다음에 오는 기차 타고
- Excuse me?
- On the next Train back.
루이스가 곤경에 처해있어. 명일 오후 즈음에
Louis is in trouble. There is every possibility
살해될 가능성이 농후해.
that he'll be dead by tomorrow afternoon.
다니엘스를 살아있는 채로 행여 다시 보고 싶으면
If you ever want to see Daniels alive again,
내 처남을 여기로 데려와.
I want my brother in law brought here.
- 그렇겐 못하지.
- 24시간 줄게.
- I can not.
- You've 24 hours.
살아날까요?
Will she survive?
모르겠어요.
I don't know.
- 아무 진전없어요.
- 깨어날까요?
- No change.
- Will she wake up?
의료진 말로는 확신할 수 없데요.
Well they say they're not sure,
- 하지만 난 그렇게 생각안하지.
- 앤-마리인가요?
- but I don't think so.
- Is that Anne-Marie?
아니요. 사고 현장에서 살아남은 사람이에요.
- No. - It's a woman that walked away from accident.
우리가 저 여자 자취를 따라가봤어요.
We followed her tracks.
아마 그녀는 앤-마리가 구해준 둘 중 한명일거에요.
Maybe she's one of the two women Anne-Marie saved.
앤-마리는 저 둘을 남겨두고 떠났어요.
She left them two.
범죄 현장 주변에 그 지역 주민들이 있어요.
Locals are at the scene.
혹시 누군가 더 있었는지 그 지역을 수색할거에요.
I'll search the area to see if there's anyone else.
앤-마리는 틀림없이 거기 있어야 해요. 그냥 사라질리가 없어요.
She has to be out there, she couldn't have just disappeared.
시신이 있어요.
There's a body.
시신?
A body?
충돌 사고 난데서 신원 미상의 여성 나왔어요.
An unidentified female person from the crash.
미안해요. 알고 있는 줄 알았는데.
I'm sorry. I thought you knew.
신원 확인 왜 안되는데요?
Why is it not identified?
- 심하게 전소되서.
- 시체 안치소에 있어요.
- She's badly burned.
- She's in the morgue.
그녀를 봐야 겠군요.
I need to see her.
에바. 잠시만. 그건 좋은 생각이 아닌거 같은데.
Eva, wait, it's not a good idea.
- 히크먼?
- 제노비즈가 전화했어.
- Hickman?
- Genovese Called.
도망쳤나요?
He escaped?
시저 두목이 그놈을 위해 일하고 있어요. 그자가 그녀의 뒷통수를 날렸어요.
Seeger's boss is working for him. Hit her from behind.
개새끼!
Son of a bitch!
에바하고 세바스찬은 지금 어디에 있는데?
Where are Eva and Sebastian right now?
지금 우리와 같이 병원에 있어요.
They are here with us at the hospital.
헬기 타러 헬리콥터 이착륙장에 15분 뒤에 가 있을거야.
I'll be at the heliport for chopper in 15.
제노비즈를 뒤 쫓을 건가요?
You going after the Genovese?
아니. 그건은 기달려야 할거야.
No, it's gonna have to wait.
빠리로 가야돼. 루이스가 위험에 쳐해있거든.
We are going to Paris, Louis is in trouble.
뭐라고요, 무슨 일인데요?
What, what's going on?
만나서 이야기 해줄께. 어서 준비나 해.
I'll tell you about it when I see you. Just be ready.
- 내보내줘요!
- 문뒤로 물러서!
- Let me out of here!
- Back away from the door!
보내줘요. 보내줘. 우리 남편이....
Let me go, let me go, my husband is...
당신 남편 나랑 같이 있는데.
Your husband is here with me!
뒤로 안물러서면 바로 여기서 내장을 다 뽑아버려!
If you don't back away, I will gut him right here!
- 물러서!
- 알았어요!
- Back off!
- Okay!
알았어요. 물러섰어요!
Okay, I'm back!
루이스? 루이스...
Louis? Louis...
Oh my God...
정신 잃지 말아요. 루이스?
Stay with me. Louis?
에바?
Eva?
못 열겠어요.
I can't open it.
- 그녀 맞아요. 토미?
- 모르겠어요.
- Is that her, Tommy?
- I don't know.
DNA를 검사해봐야 된데요. 앤-마리 어머님이 오고 계신데요.
They have to check her DNA. Anne-Marie's mother is on the way.
- 틀림없이 증거물이 있을거에요.
- 같은 생각이에요.
- There has to be proof.
- I agree.
하지만 우리는 가야 해요. 팀장이 위험에 처해있잖아요.
But we need to go. Major is in trouble.
시거 보스가 그녀를 때려 눕혔다고?
You said Seeger's boss hit her?
예. 머리에 크게 한방 맞았다더군요. 근데 아픈것보다 책임감을 더 느끼고 있어요.
Aye. She's got blow to her head, but she feels more responsible than hurt.
앤-마리 사고 현장에서 발견한 부상당한 여자가 있는데 같이 남겨뒀어요.
We left her with the injured woman we found at Anne-Marie's accident.
좋아.
Good.
사고난게 뭐가 좋아요.
There was nothing good about the accident.
그녀는 해야 할 일이 있었던거지.
She had something to do.
지금은 앤이 도와주고 있었다고 생각하자구.
Time to think Anne was helpful.
우리는 내일 오후 1시까지 밖에 시간이 없다.
We have until 1 p.m. tomorrow.
아니면 전쟁 범죄자가 교도소에서 탈출하게끔 도와줘야 돼구요?
Or we'll help a war criminal escape from prison?
둘 다 일어나면 안되지.
Which is not going to happen.
우리가 팀장과 그 부인을 찾지 못하면...
If we don't find the Major and his wife...
드미트로프가 그 둘을 처형할거야.
Dimitrov will execute the two of them.
루이스는 이 전쟁 범죄자와 무슨 관련이 있는거죠? 이.. 이 바르도프와?
What does Louis has to do with this war criminal, this this Bardov?
바르토프는 디미트로프의 처남이야.
Bardov is Dimitrov's brother in law.
그리고 디미트로프는 루이스 아들 에띠엔느 죽음에 책임이 있지.
And Dimitrov is responsible for the death of Louis' son, Etienne.
디미트로프가 다니엘 팀장의 아들을 죽였다고요?
Dimitrov killed Major Daniel's son.
그자한테 책임이 있지.
He is responsible for it.
그렇군. 우리한테 주어진 시간은 19시간 이내고 제가 뭐 빠뜨린게 없다면
Right. We have less than 19 hours, but unless I'm missing something,
어디서부터 시작해야 할지 전혀 모르는 상태구요.
we've absolutely no idea where to start.
아니. 우리한테 제대로 된 방향을 집어줄
No, we have a relationship with someone
누군가와 관계되어 있을지도 몰라.
who maybe able to point us in the right direction.
- 그런가요?
- 자네가 아는 사람있잖나. 레브 마리안스키.
- We do?
- Well, you know him. Lev Marianski.
러시아 사업가. 우리.. 우리가 프랑스 남부에서 그 사람 아들을 구해준 적이 있지.
Russian businessman. We, we rescued his son, in the south of France.
- 맞아요. 그 납치사건.
- 무슨 근거로 우릴 도와주려 하겠어요?
- Right, the kidnapping.
- Why would he help us?
그 사람이 지금 여기로 오는중이야.
He is on his way here right now.
그 사람 생각으로는 디미트로프가 중요한 인질들을 붙잡아 두는 곳이
He thinks he might give you an idea
어디인지 아이디어를 줄 수 있을거 같다고 여기는거지.
as to where Dimitrov would hold high value hostages.
우릴 도와주는 것이...
Helping us..
마리안스키 본인에게는 아주 위험할 수도 있을텐데요.
could be very dangerous for Mr. Marianski.
모든 위험에 대해 잘 알고 있다고
He made it clear to me that
그 사람이 분명히 밝혔어.
he was aware of all the risks.
이 현장 사무소는 여러분 마음대로 쓸 수 있어.
This field office is at your disposal.
그들이 제공 못하는 뭐 하나라도 있으면 그냥...
If there's anything they can't provide, just...
전화해 그럼 제공받을 수 있을거야.
call me and it'll be yours.
- 여기 계시는게 아니었어요?
- 국제형사재판소에 가야돼.
- You are not staying?
- I have to go to the ICC.
디미트로프는 바로도프가
Dimitrov knew that I had taken Bardov
감금된 이후 내가 11번 빼내왔다는 걸 알고 있어.
out of custody eleven times since he is been incarcinated
그리고 오직 7번의 공식 방문만 있었지.
and only seven visits were official.
디미트로프는 국제형사재판소 교도소 내에 정보원이 있어요.
He has a source inside the ICC prison.
그래. 그리고 바로도프 이송 건에 대한
Yes, and it's essential that at least appear
모든 준비 사항들이 최소한 들춰졌다는게 중요하지.
that making all the arrangements for his transfer.
잘해봐요들.
Good luck.
돈?
Dorn?
루이스는 레베카 때문에 자기 아들이 살해되었다는 걸 알고 있나요?
Did Louis knows that the Rebecca's the reason that their son was murdered?
바르도트는 전쟁 범죄자이잖아요.
Bardov is a war criminal.
그자의 구속과 관련된거라면 루이스는 이일과 아무런 관련이 없는거잖아요.
If this is about his imprisonment, and Louis has nothing to do with it,
그럼 레베카잖아. 레베카가
then it's Rebecca, it's Rebecca.
당신과 함께 그자를 기소했다는 이유로...
Who prosecuted him with you.
- 맞죠?
- 아니.
- Right?
- No.
- 아니라고요?
- 아니. 루이는 모르고 있어.
- No?
- No, Lui does not know.
이 사실을 자네와 나만 아는 걸로 해주면 고맙겠군.
And I would appreciate it if you could keep it between the two of us
내가 루이스에게 이 사실을 알릴 적당한 시간을 찾을때까지
until I find a suitable time I tell him.
고마워. 히크먼.
Thank you, Hickman.
우리한테 오지마.
Stay away from us.
너하고 아주 재밌게 놀거야.
I'll enjoy so much playing with you.
- 히크먼 형사님.
- 마리안스키씨...
- Detective Hickman.
- Mr. Marianski...
여기까지 와주시다니 정말 고맙습니다.
It's very good of you to come.
우리 아들을 돌려주셨잖아요.
You gave me back my son.
빚을 진 거지요.
I'm in your debt.
그리고 난 빚을 지면 갚는 사람입니다.
And I am a man who repays his debts.
도움 될만한 파일 몇가지를 가지고 왔어요.
I brought some files that maybe helpful.
내가 가지고 있던 모든 기록들이죠.
All of the records I kept.
주로 디미트로프 사업 대리인으로 역할을 했죠.
I acted mainly as Dimitrov's business agent.
건물을 알선하고 기록들을 관리하는 일이죠.
Procuring buildings and maintaining his records.
- 회계사 같은?
- 그렇죠.
- As accountant?
- Of course.
- 예?
- 디미트로프씨.
- Yes?
- Mr. Dimitrov,
마리안스키가 국제형사재판소 사무실에 도착했습니다.
Marianski has arrived at the ICC office.
- 지금 그들과 같이 있나요?
- 예. 그렇습니다.
- He is with them now?
- Yes he is.
날 배신할 사람들 중에 한 사람이라는 걸 알고 있었지.
I knew he was among those betrayed me.
일반적인 준비는 다 되었습니다.
Usual arrangements have been made.
좋아. 아주 좋아요.
Good. Very good.
디미트로프가 소유한 건물이 마치 유럽 전역에 걸쳐 있는거 처럼 보이는데.
This looks like every building Dimitrov owns in Europe.
상당한 건물을 소요하고 있지요. 하지만 모든 건물이 다 비어있는 건 아니고요.
They are quite a few, but not all of them are empty
그렇다고 모든 건물이 인질을 붙잡아 두기에 좋은 장소가 아니지요.
or good place to hold hostages.
잘 됐군요.
This is great.
상당히 범위를 좁혀 나갈 수 있겠군요.
We should be able to narrow it down quite a bit.
내가 그사람 밑에 고용되어 있던 동안에 심하게 위협받고 있었어요.
I was treated badly by him the entire time I was his employee.
우리 모두 다 그 사람의 개와 같은 존재였어요.
All of us were, We're like dogs to him.
그러니까 그가 나쁜 개주인이라 달려든다는 말인가요?
So, you're turning on him because he was a shite boss?
간단하게 말하자면 내 아들에게 넘겨주고 싶은 돈이 있어요.
Simple as I say there was a sum of money
그애한테 필요한 모든 기회를 가지고 인생을
that I liked to turn over to my boy, enough for him to start his life
시작할 수 있는 충분한 돈이죠.
with all the opportunities he could need.
하지만 디미트로프의
But I can not do that
문제가 없어질때까지는 할 수 없어요.
until Dimitrov is out of the picture.
그래서 그를 없앨려고 하고 있군?
So you're trying to get rid of him?
그 파일들을 이용해서 그사람을 집어 넣는거죠.
Use the files to put him away.
영원히.
Forever.
몸은 어때?
How do you feel?
어지럽군.
I'm dizzy.
- 조심히
- 괜찮아.
- Carefully.
- I'm fine, It's okay.
근데... 당신은 어떤데?
But...what about you?
피가 묻어 있던데
I saw blood.
가위로 놈들 중 한놈을 찔렀어요.
I stabbed one of them with scissors.
놈들한테 당신과 싸우지 말라고 경고해줄 수도 있는데 말이야.
I could told them not fighting with you.
정말 미안해요.
I'm so sorry.
그날 밤에 아파트로 돌아가면 안되는 거였는데
I should have never come back to the apartment that night.
- 멍청하고 유치한 짓이었어요.
- 사과할 필요 없어.
- That was stupid and childish.
- No apologies.
여기가 어딘지 알아?
Do you know where we are?
왜 우릴 인질로 붙잡고 있는지 이해가 안되는군.
I do not understand why take us hostage?
아마 날 이용해서 당신을 잡을려고 한거겠죠.
They probably gonna use me to get to you.
그렇다치더라도 왜 우릴 그냥 안죽이는걸까?
Yes, why not just kill us?
놈들은 계획하고 있을지 모르죠.
Maybe they're planning on it.
바로는 아닐거야.
Not for a while.
무슨 말이죠?
What do you mean?
놈들을 음식을 가져왔어. 레베카.
They brought us food, Rebecca.
우리가 살아있길 바라는 거지.
They want us alive.
당신이 우리에게 빚졌다고
You have definitely repaid us anything,
느낀 걸 확실히 우리에게 보답했군요..
that you think you might owe us.
고마워요. 도움이 되어 기뻐요.
Thank you. My pleasure.
- 조만간 다시 볼지 모르겠군요.
- 아마도.
- Maybe I'll see you soon.
- Maybe.
그렇게 생각 안한다는 건가요?
You don't think so?
디미트로프의 주의를 피하기란 거의 불가능하죠. 거의.
Very little I escape Dimitrov's attention, very little.
그사람과 사이가 틀어진 후로 쭉 감시해왔어요.
He's been watching me since we fell out.
좋은 소식은...
The good news is...
나에게 무슨 일이 생기든
Whatever happens to me,
당신이 디미트로프를 영원히 집어 넣기만 하면
if you can put Dimitrov away for good,
우리 아들에게는 틀림없이 좋은 일이죠.
my son will be more than fine.
단지...
Just...
그자는 당신 상관이나 당신들 중 그 어느 누구라도 죽일 수 있다는 걸 한치의 의심의 끈을 놓지 말아요.
don't doubt for a second that he will kill your boss or any of you.
자비를 베풀지 말아요.
Show him no mercy.
조심해요.
Be careful.
그는 우리를 도와주면 죽게 될거라는 걸 이미 알고 있었어.
He already knew he was going to get killed for helping us.
안에 들어가 있으면 훨 낫겠는데요..
Feel a lot better if we're back inside.
진짜 내가 여기있다는 걸 놈들이 알아채고 있다고는 생각지도 못했어. 토미.
Actually, I don't even think they noticed I was here, Tommy.
여전히 안전하지 못하다는 거죠?
Still not better safe, Right?
그래. 잠깐. 잠시만...
Yeah. Wait, wait a minute...
마리안스키는 디미트로프가...
He said that Dimitrov...
마리안스키는 디미트로프가 그를 감시하고 있다고 했어.
he said that Dimitrov was watching him.
확실히 그렇게 보이는데요.
Sure looks like it.
왜 마리안스키를 건물 안으로 들어가게 나뒀을까? 그리고...
Why let him to come into the building and...
우리와 대화하도록 나뒀을까?
talk to us?
명백히 마리안스키가 여기 있다는 알고 있는데 말이야.
Clearly, he knew he was here.
디미트로프는 마리안스키의 대화 상대 주체가 우리였다는 모르고 있었느지 모르죠.
Maybe he did not know it was us he was coming to talk to.
디미트로프가 프랑스 팀장을 납치한 같은날
He left the shit over a bunch of files
그자는 많은 파일을 남겨놓고
and went to an ICC field office on the same day
국제헌법재판소 현장 사무실로 향했어?
that Dimitrov kidnaps a French Major?
그자는 마리안스키가 우리에게 말한다는걸 알고도 걱정하지 않는것 처럼 보이는데요.
It's like he was not in worried about what he was going tell us.
쓸만한 파일은 없다는 말이 되는군.
There's probably nothing on those files that we can use.
그럼 다시 원점으로 돌아가는거네요.
Then we're back to zero.
무기로 쓸만한 아무거나.
Anything we can use as a weapon.
느슨하게 빠진 벽돌이나 유리 조각 같은거...
Loose brick, a piece of glass...
벽속에 뭐가 들어 있는지 알고 싶지도 않아.
I do not even want to know what's in the walls.
저놈들이 날 이방에서 데리고 나갈 구실을 만들 뭔가가 필요해.
We need something to make them take me out of this room.
뭐? 여기에 날 혼자 남겨두겠다고요?
What? You leave me here alone?
현 상황에서는 그렇게라도 해야지. 걱정말고.
Just as it is necessary. Do not worry.
- 좀 먹어둬야지.
- 아니. 됐어요.
- You should eat.
- No, thanks.
어서 그냥 빵이잖아.
Come on, just a bread.
저놈들이 이런식으로 죽이지 않는다고 확신해요?
Are you sure they are not trying to kill us this way?
- 루이?
- 이게 될만도...
- Lui?
- This is could be...
이걸 써요.
Use this.
잠시만!
Wait!
날 내보내줘!
Let me out of here!
거기 날 좀 내보내 달라고!
Hey, let me out of here!
Keep your goods about, you know this is not the place to let you defense down.
경계 풀지마고 있어.
Stay alert.
- 지금 바르도프를 데려오고 있는 중입니다.
- 고마워요.
- Bringing Bardov from now, Sir.
- Thank you.
이놈들 다 이곳에 집어넣으셨습니까?
Did you put all these men in here, sir?
전부는 아니고.
Not all.
전쟁 범죄자들이잖습니까?
They are war criminals?
아니 그들 중 몇은 그냥 기소만 됐지.
No, some of them are just accused.
아직 재판장에 서지도 않았어.
Haven't stood trial yet.
유죄가 선고되면 그들에게 합당한 교도소가 담판지어 지겠지.
If they are convicted, a proper prison will be negociated for them.
전에는 악마를 절대 믿지 않았지만...
You know, I've never really believed in evil before, but it's...
조셒 콘래드 작품에 대해 잘 알고 있나?
Are you familiar with the writings of Joseph Conrad?
아닙니다.
No, sir.
"악의 초자연적 근원에 대한 존재의
"The belief in a supernatural source of evil
믿음은 필요하지 않다.
is not necessary.
인간은 혼자서도 모든 악을 행할 수 있다."
Men alone are quite capable of every wickedness."
그가 썼지.
He wrote that.
잠시만.
Excuse me.
- 마리안스키가 도움은 좀 됐나?
- 죽었어요.
- Was Marianski helpful?
- He's dead.
Oh God...
빌딩 바로 밖에서 총을 맞고 쓰러졌어요.
Gunned down right outside of our building.
그렇게 될지 알고 있었더라고요.
He knew that known.
놈들이 따라붙었다 그더러라고요.
Well, he said that he is being followed.
그사람한테 말했나?
You spoke to him?
예. 그사람이 우리에게 말한 후 떠나면서 살해당했어요.
Oh yeah, he was killed as he was leaving, after he talked to us.
Oh my god.
예. 디미트로프는 그사람이 우리에게 말하도록 나눈거죠.
Yeah, Dimitrov let him talk to us.
마리안스키가 빌딩내에 있을 때 죽일 수도 있었는데 말이죠.
They could kill him while he was in the building.
근데 디미트로프는 마리안스키가 당신 팀에 말하는걸 걱정안했던 거지.
But Dimitrov wasn't worried about what Marianski would tell you,
왜냐하면 디미트로프는 마리안스키가 알지 못하는 곳에 팀장 내외를 붙잡고 있을테니까.
because he is holding them somewhere Marianski wouldn't know.
아마 그들 사이가 틀어지고 나서 디미트로프가 그 건물을 샀을수도 있겠군.
Maybe it's a building that Dimitrov bought after they fell out.
지난 몇년 내?
In the past few years?
그게 정확히 내가 알고 싶었던 겁니다.
That's exactly what I needed to know.
고맙습니다.
Thank you, sir.
좋아. 지금부터 우리는 지난 2년간 이뤄진
Okay, we are looking for real estate transaction made
부동산 거래를 살펴볼거야.
in the last two years.
마리안스키가 알지 못하는 그런거.
Something that Marianski wouldn't know anything about.
지난 2년간 그가 한것이라곤
All he has done in the last two years,
전부 처분한 것밖에 없는데요. 돈을 긁어 모으는거처럼 보이던데요.
is divest himself of everything, it's like he is cashing out.
그 시기에 그가 한것이라곤 오직 하나 밖에 없어요.
The only thing that he's bought at all in this time
런더 마이너리그 풋볼 클럽이네요.
I'm afraid is a London minor league football club.
- 풋볼 클럽?
- 그쪽에선 사커라 부르죠.
- Football club?
- You call it soccer.
풋볼 클럽이 뭔지 나도 알아.
I know what a football club is.
경기장도 같이 샀나?
Did he buy the club with the stadium?
에지웨어에 있는 흑호(黑虎) 경기장이네요.
"Black Tiger Stadium" in Edgware.
하지만 우리는 런던 근처에도 가지 못할거야.
But we're not gonna be able to get around London
누군가의 도움 없이는, 핵심 인물이면서 중요한 누군가의 도움 없이는
without the help of someone, someone of the matter, someone important.
경감님?
Sir?
돈씨라는데요!
Dorn, sir!
뭐? 뭐라고 했어?
What? What did you say?
죄송하지만 경감님. 말씀하시길
Sorry, Chief Inspector, you told me,
국제헌법재판소의 돈이라는 사람으로부터 전화가 오면
if I ever got a call from a man named Dorn from ICC,
즉시 연락하고 하셔서.
to contact you immediately.
자네가 부른건가?
Is that you singing?
돈. 이 나쁜놈같으니라고.
Dorn, oh you slut.
내 주중 가라오께 행사중에 전화를 하는거야. You call me on my weekly karaoke indulgence.
You call me on my weekly karaoke indulgence.
- 거기 경감나리께서는 잘 나가시나?
- 사람들이 날 좋아해.
- Was the Chief Inspector going well?
- The crowd Loves me.
사람들은 우리가 스파이스 걸스 노래 부르는 걸 좋아하잖아!
They are interested to see we both singing the bloody Spice Girls!
그건 그렇고 거기는 가벼운 농담 따먹기 하는 사람이 아닌데??????????? Anyhow, listen, you're not one for a casual catchup.
Anyhow, listen, you're not one for a casual catchup.
뭘 해드릴까?
What can I do?
뭘 좀 도와줬으면 하는데.
I need you to help me with something.
칼 히크먼, 빅토리아, 버거, 맥코널입니다.
Karl Hickman, Vitoria, Berger, McConnell.
- 마일스 레넌 경감이요.
- 예.
- Chief Inspector Myles Lennon.
- Yeah.
런던에 온 걸 환영해요.
Welcome to London.
- 거기 의자에 앉아보게.
- 예.
- Sit in the chair there.
- Yes, sir.
누군가요?
Who is he?
엔써레예스 숀.
Enthereyes Shawn.
- 고맙네.
- 이게 다입니까?
- Thank you.
- That's all?
- 그래.
- 뭘 잘못했나요?
- Yes.
- I failed?
아니 전혀. 실은 완벽해.
No, not at all. Actually, you're perfect.
밖에서 기다리게.
Wait outside.
그리고 내 충고 명심하게.
And remember my admonitions.
예.
Yes, sir.
한 방에서 자네 둘을 같이 보고 싶었거든.
I wanted to see the two of you in the same room
크기와 키가 같은지 확인하고 싶어서
to confirm that you are of the same size and height.
왜 내 유인용 미끼가 필요한데?
Why would you need a decoy of me?
자네 매형이 나와 아주 소중한 사람을 납치해갔거든.
Your brother in law has taken prisoner people who very dear to me.
그게 나랑 무슨 관련이 있는데?
How is that my concern?
왜냐하면 그가 말하길 자네 탈출을 도와주면 내 사람들을 풀어주겠다더군.
Because he said he would let them go if I helped you to escape.
- 뭐라고?
- 그리고 더 있는데.
- What?
- And more than that.
우리가 함께 남겨진 때를 다 알고 있어.
He knows every time we've left here together.
정확히 다.
Precisely every time.
그 개새끼가 날 죽이고 싶어 하는군.
Son of a bitch wants to kill me.
그렇지.
Exactly.
내가 어떻게 도와주면 되는데?
How can I help you?
런던 경시청에 오신 걸 환영해요.
Welcome to New Scotland Yard.
좋아. 국제헌법재판소에 온 여기 젊은이들과 숙녀분들이고 이 사람들이
Right, these lads and ladies are from the ICC and they need our help
러시아 마피아들한테서 자기네 팀장 내외를 구출하는데 우리의 도움이 필요하단거지.
in rescueing their leader and his wife from a Russian gangsters.
삼류 스릴러같은 이야기인데요.
Sounds like a bloody Penny Dreadful.
누가 이 이야기를 오페라로 쓰라고 알려줬지.
Someone remind me to write an Opera about this.
정말로 나중에 나한테 상기시켜줄려고 필기하지 않을거지?
You're not actually writing that down for reminding me, right?
여기 몇명은 조금 잘 속아넘어가지만 이 방에 있는 대부분은
Some of them are a tad gullible, but many of them in this room
자기 업무에 최고들이지.
are the best we have at their jobs.
전술, 통신, 정보 처리.
Tactical, comms, cover intelligence.
이 사람들에게 최신 정보를 알려주도록.
Bring them up to date.
경기장 주변 CCTV 영상을 돌려봤는데
We rewound the CCTV images around the stadium.
지난 24시간 내에 움직임이 있었습니다만 12시간 내에는 없었어요.
and there has been movement in the last 24 hours, but not in the last 12.
우리 팀장하고 부인은 봤나요?
Did you see Major or his wife?
차 몇 대가 가까이 세워져 있어요.
A couple of vehicles parked close.
사람들이 한 사람 주변에 있었는데 아주 재빠르게 움직이고 있어요.
Mens around one figure and they rushed through quickly.
하지만 뚜렷이 볼 수 없었죠.
But we couldn't get a very good look.
얼마나 되나요?
How many?
적어도 확실히 열명의 사람들이 들락거렸어요.
At least ten unique figures moving in and out,
하지만 내부에 얼마나 많은 인원이 배치되었는지 알 도리는 없고요.
but there's no way to know how many are posted inside.
이게 경기장 도식화면인가요?
Is this the schematic of the stadium?
그래요. 하지만 10년도 넘은거라서
Yeah, but they are more than ten years old.
이 건물은 거의 같은 시기만큼 페쇄되어 있었고 황폐해진 상태죠.
the buildings been closed for almost that long and fallen into disrepair.
아래는 어떻게 되었는지 알 수가 없죠.
No one knows what it looks like below.
황폐요? 아주 좆같이 보이는데.
Disrepair? Looks like a pair of shite.
맥코널 맞지? You're McConnell?
You're McConnell?
예. 경찰...
Yeah. The Police Services...
북 아일랜드. 자네 가족을 잘 알고 있지.
Northern Ireland. I know your family very well.
어떻게요?
How?
그 답을 잘 알고 있으리라 여길게. 애송이.
Reckon you know the answer to that, Tinker.
- 이제 질문 하나만 남았는데.
- 어떤거?
- Only one question remaining.
- Which is?
CCTV 영상에 보이는 사람들 중에 없던데
Since none of them are seen on the camera,
당신네 대장이 내부에 있다는 걸 확신하나요?
are you sure that your boss is even inside?
아니요. 확신한다고는 말 못하겠는데요.
No, I can not really say for sure.
오직 이 장소만이 타당한 곳이에요.
It's the only place that makes sense.
미안하지만 난 "오직 이 장소만이 타당한 곳이에요."에
I'm Sorry, I can not authorise a major raid
근거해서 대규모 공습을 허가할 수 없어.
based on "It's the only place that makes sense".
나하고 문제가 있어서 인가요?
Because you got a problem with me?
- 그런말 한 적 없어.
- 우린 시간이 많이 않아요.
- I never said that.
- We do not have a lot of time.
잘 알고 있어요!
I'm aware of that!
하지만 우리 사람들을 위험에 투입하기 전에 구체적인 정보가 필요해요.
But I need concrete knowledge before I put any of my people at risk.
카메라 몇 개를 안에 들여놓을 방법이 있을지 모르겠네요.
I may have a way to get some cameras inside.
그것들을 가지고 왔어요?
You brought Them?
몇 개만.
A few.
할 수 있겠어요?
You can do that?
경기장 주변 건물하고 저격용 라이플이 필요합니다.
We need to use the buildings around the stadium and a sniper rifle.
날 내보내줘!
Let me out of here!
죽을 때까지 소리쳐도 상과없어. 아무도 못 듣거든.
You can scream forever, no one can hear you.
- 저리 꺼져!
- 오~ 깡이 있네.
- Piss off!
- Oh, you have spirit.
경찰 남편이 당신 깡에 대해 잘 알고 있나?
Does your cop husband appreciate your spirit?
아닐걸.
I don't think so.
잘 알고 있지도 못할걸.
I don't think he appreciate it at all.
엿 먹어!
Screw you!
엿 먹으라고?
Screw me?
왜 너같은 여자들은 항상
Why do women like you always think that
나같은 남자보다 항상 훨씬 잘났다고 생각할까?
they are so much better than a man like me?
이게 좋아? 이런거 좋아해? You love this? You love this.
You love this? You love this.
그래도 이런거느...
But you'd better not to part...
넌 죽을 줄 알아.
You gonna die for this.
- 넌 다음이고!
- 안돼!
- You're next!
- No!
당신네 세바스찬...
This Sebastian of yours...
그의 카메라가 작동할까요?
His cameras are gonna work?
그가 실패해서 웃어본적이 없어서...
Never seen a gasser of his failed.
웃기겠군.
Would be fun.
아무래도 부족하지요 근데????? Enough for nothing, but...
Enough for nothing, but...
맥코널...
McConnell...
그는 좋은 사람이에요.
He's good.
얼마나 알고 지냈나요?
How long you do know him?
6개월요.
Six months.
그의 진정한 모습을 모른다고 생각하나요?
You think I don't know the real him?
우습군요.
That's funny.
내면이 선한 사람이에요. 선하다는게 중요한거죠.
He's good inside. The good where it counts.
그 손이 괴롭히나요?
Bothering you?
평소와 마찬가지죠 뭐.
No more than usual.
지금 약에 취해 있나요?
You high right now?
예민한 질문이네요.
That's subtle.
난 당신과 함께 무장한 용의자들과 맞설거에요.
I'm going up against armed suspects with you.
현 상황을 알고 싶은데요.
I want to know the situation.
진통제를 먹고 있지만 예전것처럼 세지 않네요.
I take painkillers, but they aren't as strong as they use to be.
몰핀 패치 대신 코데인 알약을 쓴다고요. 알고 있어요.
Codeine pills instead of Morphine patches, I know.
당신들이 도착하기전 당신 모두 다 조사해봤어요.
I researched you all before you arrived.
무슨... 인터넷 사이트에 내 처방 내역이 올라가 있나요?
What... the website has my prescription history?
돈이 약간의 귀뜸도 해주었지요.
Also Dorn give me a little bit heads up.
당신과 타미처럼 항상 의견이 일치하는 건 아니니까요.
Well, like you and Tommy, we don't always see eye to eye.
실은 당신은 내가 믿어야만 할 판단력을 가졌던 사람이고 그가 말해줬어요.
Actually he did tell me that you were someone who's judgement I should trust.
그거면 당신에게 충분한가요?
That's good enough for you?
무언가에, 기관에 평생을
I know, you know, how it feels
몸바친다게 어떤지 나도 알아요.
to devote your life to something, to an institution,
그러고 나면 바로 그것들이 당신을 완전히 배신하게되죠.
and then just had them betrayed you completely.
하지만 당신을 믿는 누군가가 있다는 게 어떤지 알고 있나요?
But do you know how it feels to have someone believing you.
내 말은 단지 믿는게 아니고 앞으로 나아가는거
I mean not just believe, but to step up,
영원히 잃어버렸다고 생각했던 걸 당신에게 돌려주는 그런 거요.
give you back the things that you thought you are gonna lose forover.
절망에 직면한 희망이죠.
Hope in the face of despair.
이번 일이 끝나고 나면
When this is over,
돈이 포클랜드 제도에서 날위해 뭘 해줬는지 이야기할 수 있을지도 모르겠군요.
maybe I'll tell you what Dorn did for me in the Falkland Islands.
하지만 지금은...
But for now...
그래요. 돈의 말이면 충분해요.
yeah, his word is good enough for me.
맥코널 가족을 거의 내 평생 경찰 생활동안 알고 있었어요.
I've known the Mcconnell family for almost all my professional life.
내말을 믿어요.
Trust me when I tell you that
그 가족들 어느 누구도 당신 말처럼 선함을 중요히 여기지 않아요.
none of them are as you say it good inside where it counts.
저 개소리하는 재수없는 새끼가 날 판단한다고 생각하는 사람이 누구야?
Who's that gobshite tosser thinking he is judging me?
이봐. 난 저사람을 변호할려고 했던게 아니야. 근데 저사람 생각도 일리가 있어.
Look, I'm not trying to defend him or any thing, but he's got a point.
내 말은 당신 가족과 업무상있었던 전력이 있을 수도 있잖아.
I mean he's probably has some professional runnings with your family.
- 불쾌한 전력이겠지.
- 이런게 그 사람을 옹호하는게 아니라고?
- Unpleasant ones, I imagine.
- This is you not defending him?
얼마나 많은 사람들이 우리 아버지에 대해 물어보는지 알아?
Do you know how many times people question me about my father?
그래서 뭐? 그건 옳지 않아.
So what? That doesn't make it right.
그래. 근데 피할 수 없잖아.
No, but it makes it inevitable.
좋아요. 짐 꾸립시다. All right. Let's pack up.
All right. Let's pack up.
아무도 신경쓰지 않는다면 여기 라이플을 든 아일랜드 청년이
And if nobody minds, I'd rather not having this Belfast boy
내 뒤에 서있는 걸 원치 않아서 말이죠.
stand behind me with a rifle.
당신 아가리를 닥치게 할려고 뒤에 서 있을 필요 없어.
I don't need to be behind you to end your big mouth.
진정해. 농담이야. 그냥 긴장을 풀고 싶어서 그런거야.
Chill, joke, just tring to ease the tense.
그럼 어거 가서 당신네 대장을 찾아야지.
Come on, then, let's go find your boss.
무겁네. 벗겨.
Heavy boy. Take that off.
Come on! Come on!
카메라는 이 저속 라이플 탄환속에 있어요.
The cameras are inside these low velocity rifle rounds.
- 농담하는 게 아니군.
- 전에 몇 번 해봤는데 먹혔어요.
- You aren't kidding.
- We've tried them, they work.
저속탄은 단지 한가지 문제가 있는데
There is only one real problem with low velocity.
- 바람!
- Wind!
Two paral, gorgeous.
사격은 어디서 배웠나?
Where did you learn to shoot?
우리 아버지한테서.
My dad taught me.
당신 동료들로부터 보호하기 위해
To protect us from your pals.
오케이 타미. 창문을 하나 찍어. 바람이 불어 오고 있어.
OK, Tommy, pick a window, the wind is coming.
- 나이스 샷.
- 영상을 받아볼 수 있길 바라자고.
- Nice shot.
- Let's hope we get an image.
봐봐.
Look.
시거 경찰관.
Officer Seeger.
시거 경찰관?
Officer Seeger?
죄송합니다.
I'm sorry, Sir.
내가 누군지 아나?
Do you know who I am?
물론이죠. 던커스 지방 총경님이시죠.
Of course, Regional Commander Dunkers.
당신 상관 버건의 소재지를 알려 주러 왔네.
I came to tell you we've located your boss Commander Bergen.
체포하신 겁니까?
Have you arested him?
정확히는 자살했다고 해야지.
Apparently he shot himself.
사망했나요?
He's dead?
감당하기엔 너무 커다란 수치심이 그를 따라 붙고 있었지. The shame after that was too much for him to have.
The shame after that was too much for him to have.
인질로 잡히는 상태보다는 탈출을 선택.
Being taken as hostage in an escape.
적어도 내가 읽은 보고서의 내용을 그렇네.
At least, there's on the report I read.
죄수가 탈출하는데 도와준 사람입니다.
He helped the prisoner escape.
그 사람이 죽고 나서 그렇게 한다고 한들 뭐가 달라지지?
What different does that make now, since he's dead.
하지만 그런 사실이 아니지 않습니까?
But that isn't the truth.
우리는 경찰이네. 시거. 우리가 말하는 게이 사실이지.
We're the police, Seeger, the truth is what we say it is.
우리 이 작은 부서로는 감다하기 힘든 스캔들이네.
Our small department can't afford this scandal and
그리고 자네가 이해해줄거라 확신하네만.
I'm sure you understand that.
경위?
Inspector?
고맙네. 자넨 현명한 결정을 한거야.
Thank you, you made a wise choice.
총경님. 그 사람은 지금 어디에 있습니까?
Sir, where is he now?
시체 안치소에 있네.
He's at the morgue.
그일에 신경 쓰지 말고 집에 가서 쉬게. 자넨 그럴만하네.
But don't concern youself with that, go home have a rest. You've earned it.
이름은 바르도프. 내 보호 감찰 하에 풀어주는 주는 거네. 미카엘 레크냐 돈.
His name is Bardov, he has been released in my custody, Mikael Lechnya Dorn,
국제헌법재판소 검사.
ICC prosecutor.
서류는 공증되었소.
Documents are notarized.
지금 떠나고 있어요.
He's leaving.
차에 실어.
Stripe him in.
예?
Yes?
바르토프를 데리고 있어.
I have Bardov.
벨기에에 있는 주소를 문자 보낼거요.
I've text you the address in Belgium.
거기 도착할려면 몇 시간걸리걸요.
It should take several hours to get there.
도착하면 들어와서 정차하시오.
When you arrive, pull in.
그러면 내 차가 보일거요.
And you'll see my vehicle.
3시간 뒤에 그자들이 도착할거야. They will be there in three hours.
They will be there in three hours.
거기 온 자들 다 죽이도록.
I want everyone who comes dead.
모두 다
Everyone.
이게 마지막이야. 토미.
This is the last one, Tommy.
고마워. 더 많은 압박감이 필요했었거든.
Thanks. Needed more pressure.
그래. 하지만 우리는 여전히 팀장의 흔적도 없고
Yes, but we still leave no trace of the Major,
이제 두 시간도 채 남지 않았어.
and no at least couples of hours left.
바람이 불어 오고 있어.
Wind is coming.
무슨 일이야?
What the hell is that?
모르겠는데요.
I don't know.
이제 명백히 발생했어요.
Now that's definitely happened.
살아 있고.
He is alive.
간신히
Barely.
시간이 좀 필요해.
I need some time.
- 우린 시간이 별로 없어요.
- 지금 우리가 움직이면
- Well we don't have time.
- If we move now,
우리가 들어왔다는 걸 디미트로프가 알아챌거야.
Dimitrov will know we just get in part of.
놈들이 돌아가서 숨어버리면 이짓을 계속 해야 되는거야.
They'll just go back and hide in, and this will just continue.
시간이 얼마나 필요하신데요?
How much time do you need?
30분. 30분이면 돼. 그럼 끝날거야. 끝이 날거야.
30 minutes, just 30 minutes and this will be done, it will be over.
- 영원히
- 최선을 다해볼게요. 돈.
- Forever.
- I'll do our best, Dorn,
하지만 이건 말해야 겠네요.
but I got to tell you something that
팀장이 30분을 버틸지 모르겠네요.
I don't know if he's gonna lest in 30 minutes.
자살한 경감 버건 맞나요?
Is this the cop, Commander Bergen, commit suicide?
자살? 그사람들이 DT로 인해 사망한 사람 중 하나라고 그랬던거 같은데.
Suicide? I thought they said he was killed one of D.T..
인질을 잡고 있던가 뭐
taken hostage or something like that.
총기 발사 잔여물이 남아있지 않은 자살한 경우를 본 적 있나요?
Have you seen a suicide not leaving any gunshot residue?
자살에 대해선 잘 몰라서요.
I don't know about suicide.
내가 아는 거라곤 부검을 하고 싶지 않는 거지요.
All I know is it don't want any autopsia.
우리는 경찰이야. 우리가 말하는 게 사실이 되는거네.
We're the police. The truth is what we say it is.
이걸로 끝이야.
This is ending.
근데 끝내기 전에
But before it ends,
니 마누라하고 좋은 시간 좀 보낼거야.
I'm gonna spend some precious time with your wife.
알려주고 싶어서.
I want you to know that.
아내를 손대면 죽여버린다.
If you touch my wife, I will kill you.
웃기고 있네.
Now, that's funny.
놈들 중 한 놈이 팀장을 다시 때렸어.
One of them just hit the Major again.
좀 더 구체적으로 어떤놈인지 확인해봐.
Be more specific which one.
내가 그놈한테 뭔가 특별한걸 선사해줘야지.
I'd give him something special.
얼굴에 피 뭍은 놈
With blood on his face.
히크먼. 가야 돼요.
Hickman, we gotta go.
뭔 일인데?
What's going on?
팀장 혼자서 풀고 놈들을 쫒고 있어요.
Major got himself free he's going after them himself.
예. 히크먼...
Yes, Hickman...
상황이 바뀌었어요. 출동해야 돼요.
Things have changed, Dorn, we gotta move.
구해내야해. 그들을 구해내.
Save them. save them.
레넌!
Lenone!
워록? 줄서! 출동하자!
Warlock? Line up! let's go to work!
최대한 빨리 이동해!
Come as fast as you can!
이제 놈들에게 우리가 오고 있다는 알려준 셈이군.
Right, that's gonna let them know we're coming.
히크먼. 맥코널 데리고 오른쪽으로 가세요.
Hickman take Mcconnell go to the right,
- 나머지는 다 왼쪽으로 이동.
- 예. 이쪽으로
- the rest of you all make to the left.
- Yes, this way.
이리와.
Come.
도착했어.
We're here.
같이 일하게 돼서 기쁘군. 돈.
Pleasure doing business with you, Dorn.
이건 하나도 기쁘지 않은데
Nothing about this has been a pleasure.
그렇게 느끼다니 진심으로 유감이군.
Truely sorry you feel that way.
당신을 어린애를 목표를 삼았어.
You target to the child.
뭔가 좀 시끌벅적하게 하고 싶었거든.
I want you to do something louds.
다니엘스 가족은 당신 약점이잖아.
The Daniels family were your weakness.
그 아이는 부차적 피해자지.
The boy was collateral damage.
잘가게. 돈.
Goodbye, Dorn.
끝났네.
It's over.
어떻게...
How did you...
드론이라는게 단지 차만 원격으로 작동하는게 아니거든.
Drone is not the only vehicle can be operated remotely.
어떻게 날 찾았지?
How did you find me?
거의 헐벗은 아가씨가 있는
We had satellite tracking you
바에서 만난 후로 위성으로 추적했지.
ever since we met at a bar with nearly naked ladies.
우린 루이스와 레베카를 되찾아왔지. 그 내외는 안전해.
We've recovered Louis and Rebecca. They are safe.
바르도프는 다시 감방으로 돌아갔어. 이거 들어봐.
Bardov is back in his cell. listen to this.
뭔가 좀 시끌벅적하게 하고 싶었거든.
I wanted to do something louds.
다니엘스 가족은 당신 약점이잖아.
The Daniels family were your weakness.
그 아이는 부차적 피해자지.
The boy was collateral damage.
당신한테는 항복할 기회이고
This is your chance to surrender and
카트야와 다니엘의 살인에 대한 혐의로 맞닥뜨려야 할거야.
face the charge for the murder of Katya and Daniel.
항복?
Surrender?
돈... 당신은 지금 우리나라에 들어와 있어.
Dorn... you're in my country.
도대체 무슨 생각으로 당신은 나에게 국경을 넘어와서 그런 걸 제시하는데?
How the hell do you think you would ever give me across the border.
내가 이쪽 수익을 쥐고 있어.
I own this revenue.
좀 더 정확히 말한다면...
It would be more accurate to say...
"내 매형은 툴리아와 그 주변 지역의 모든 범죄에 대한 책임이 있어요.
"My brother-in-law own all the criminals of Tulia and the area around it.
하지만 난 제안하지 그자들로부터 바르도프을 보호하겠다고"
But I'm offering you his protection from them."
날 체포하겠다고?
Better arresting me?
내 처남은 우리 사람들을 배신했어.
My brother-in-law is a traitor to his people.
그놈 죽는 날도 얼마 안남았어.
His days are numbered.
마지막으로. 나랑 같이 가면 살 수 있어.
Last time, come with me and you will live.
안그런다면 당신 안전을 보장 못해.
If you don't, I can not guarantee your safety.
꺼져.
Go to hell.
러시아를 벗아날 수 있다고 생각하면
And if you think you would ever get out of Russia,
늙은만큼이나 멍청한거야.
you are as foolish as you are old.
그래도 난 내일을 늙어가면서 맞겠지만 당신을 아닐걸.
But tomorrow I'll be older. And you will not.
전화 한통이면. 돈! 한 통만 하면!
One call, Dorn! One call!
그러면 당신을 이 숲을 벗어나지 못할걸! 절대로!
And you will not leave this wood! Never!
우릴 위해 올 줄 알았어. 칼.
I knew you'll come for us, Carl.
고맙네.
Thank you.
질문... 질문을 받았어요. 오늘. 다른 그 누구도 믿지 않을 때
Who was asked today asked today if I knew what it was like,
누군가가 나를 믿고 있다는 걸 알고 있으면 어떨지.
to have someone believes in me when no one else did.
굉장한 하루였어!
What a day, huh!
잘했어들 모두.
Good job, everybody.
국제헌법재판소. 히크먼입니다.
ICC, Hickman.
확실해요?
Are you sure?
예. 고마워요.
Yeah, thanks. Thank you.
앤-마리 어머님이 오셨다는군.
Anne-marie's mother went to the morgue.
이미 처리된 DNA 샘플을 가지고
with the DNA samples already processed.
벌...써요? 어떻게 그렇게 빨리?
Al... already? how can it be so fast?
의사셨다는데.
Her mother was a doctor.
앤-마리가 어렸을적에 유전적으로 자폐증 테스트를 하셨대.
She had Anne-marie genetically tested for autism when she was a kid.
그럼 그...
So then the...
- DNA는...
- 일치한다는군.
- The DNA is...
- It's a match.
그럼 그 시신은 앤-마리라구요?
So, the body is Anne-marie?
시신은 옮겨 싣고 프랑스로 되돌아 가는 중이라는군.
Body got picked up two hours ago. It's on the way back to France.
전화기를 깜박 했네.
I forgot my phone.
- 거기서 봐.
- OK.
- See you there.
죄송해요 전화기를 놓고 와서요.
I'm sorry, I just forgot my phone.
- 괜찮으세요?
- 어. 그래. 괜찮아.
- You okay?
- Yeah, yeah, I'm fine.
아주 특별하게 될 사람인데요.
She was gonna be a special one.
영리했지.
She was smart.
정말 많은 질문을 해댔지.
She asked a lot of questions.
- 좋은 질문들도.
- 제대로 된 것들.
- And good ones.
- Do right parts.
그렇죠.
Yes.
나도 알아요.
I know.
이 팀이 사작하는 시점으로 돌아가보면
Back at the beginning of this team.
루이스가 다시 경찰을 기분을 느끼고 싶지 않냐고 물어봤었지.
Louis asked me if I wanted to feel like a cop again.
그래서 찾았지.
I did find that.
- 대부분.
- 대부분?
- Mostly.
- Mostly?
이런 부분은 내가 취하지 않았지.
This part I didn't take.
누군가를 잃은 부분
The part when you lose someone.
내 생각에는...
I guess...
우리 모두 다 혼자였던거죠.
we were all kind of alone
팀장이 우릴 하나의 팀으로 만들 당시에
when the Major put all of us together.
난 그랬어요.
I was.
세바스찬, 토미...
Sebastian, Tommy...
당신도 당신만의 것들이 있었죠.
You had your own things.
절대된 표현이군.
That's an understatement.
아마도 팀장이 다시 경찰이 되는 기분이라는 건
Maybe what he meant by feeling, like a cop again.
가족의 일부가 되는것일 수도
is being in part of the family.
당신이 가족이라면 때로는 사람을 잃기도 하잖아요.
When you're family, sometimes you lose people.
그래도 혼자서 잃지 말아요.
But you don't have to lose them alone.
그럴지도.
Maybe.
우리랑 같이 가서 한잔 해요? 앤-마리를 위해
Why don't you come with us for a drink? For Anne-Marie.
그래.
OK.
이제 우리는 가족이 됐으니 칼튼은 그만 불러도 되겠네요?
Maybe now that we're a family, I can stop calling you Carlton?
- 아닐수도.
- OK. 아닐수도.
- Or not.
- OK. Or not.